The children are covered in [ __ ].  There is no water, no gas,
no electricity.  We drink in a dirty
pool right in the rainwater.  My husband
tried to poison me this morning, but let's take things in
order.  I woke up this morning to
my husband Danil bringing me
breakfast in bed.  To be honest, I
thought he was poisoned, but no, he seems to be
alive.  Then the lights went out, the
wind and rain started.  As soon as we have bad
weather, for some reason the lights go out right away
.  I wonder why she wanted to cook food for the dogs at least
while there is no water in the house, since the
pump is not working due to the lack of
electricity.  But there was
also no water coming from the drinking tap, which operates without a pump.  But
this is to my advantage, because I have had
such a huge pile of dishes standing there since the day before yesterday,
and I won’t be doing them today.  Have you pooped?  Yes,
of course, where would we be without it.  The children decided to
[ __ ] themselves as soon as the lights and water went out.  I had to wash them
outside, I couldn’t leave them in that
state.  Eva ran barefoot down the
street, picking up a bunch of blisters.
Danil and I, having nothing else to
do, decided to splash around in the pool.
We splashed around, washed ourselves, and had a blast.
Then I remembered that someone wrote that
I was a mammon who escaped from the Ice
Age.  It seems.